onlygirlsgames.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy

The following is the official privacy policy for [www.onlygirlsgames.com](http://www.onlygirlsgames.com/) , a website centered around flash games and child-friendly content, suitable for children and teens. This Privacy Policy covers the issues related to personal information collected by the site and information regarding tracking and information collection from our affiliates, advertisers and partners.

**Collection of Personal Information** \- At [www.onlygirlsgames.com](http://www.onlygirlsgames.com/), we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important and we take every measure to keep you informed on how we collect, safeguard and use your personal data, where applicable. We never sell your personal information to third parties, however our site might run scripts (such as Google Analytics) that collect log file information for analytical and statistical reports. The kind of information these third parties collect include your IP address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser you visit our site with (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc), the pages you visit and the time you spend on pages of our site. This information is used strictly for ourselves, using it to better improve our site’s performance and user experience. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** \- Cookies are small text files that are placed in the visitor's computer with the purpose of storing their preferences. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive, they are purely "shortcuts" that allow web sites to remember users activities on a web site as well as users visits to a site. Since we use third party advertisements to support [www.onlygirlsgames.com](http://www.onlygirlsgames.com/), there is a chance the companies running these ads might store your data in cookies, in order to collect advertisement information or protect you from abusive advertising (for example, stopping pop-up scripts from running multiple times from your IP). Because these advertisement companies may also collect the personal information stated above, we at [www.onlygirlsgames.com](http://www.onlygirlsgames.com/) make sure we only use trustworthy 3rd parties, in order to protect our users.

In general, these cookies and web beacons are used for research purposes and for geo-targeting and behavioral targeting of the ads. If you feel uncomfortable providing this kind of information to our advertisers through cookies, you can turn them off from your preferred browser’s settings, or manage them through Internet Security software (such as Norton Internet Security for example).

Onlygirlsgames.com displays adverts on all of our pages, from Google Adsense and Valueclick. These Advertisers offers child safe targeted ads to our users.

We have child friendly filters in place with Google Adsense and Valueclck so that only child safe adverts are shown. If however, there are any inappropriate adverts displayed we would kindly ask a guardian or a parent to contact us so we can investigate further.

Google is also using the DART cookie to collect information about every user. This cookie does not store any personal data or sensitive information and can be removed by you searching the cookie in the cookies folder of your browser on your PC

**External Links** \- Our site has several external links pointing to our partners, or the flash games we post on our site might have in-game links to other sites that might offer content that we have no control over. Unfortunately, we cannot take responsibility for the content shown by our partners, although we only pick to link to related, quality websites that are non-intrusive and offer clean content suitable for our target audience.

**Parents -** We do not collect any personal information from your children such as age, location, etc. We also do not employ a chat room or private messaging service on this website. We do employ a filter on any comments made on our website which filter out any swear words. If you come across any inappropriate comments or content then please let us know and we will remove them immediately. If you would like any information regarding our website then please contact us. Please remember the internet can be a dangerous place for a child so be vigilant of their browsing habits.

**Copyright -** we have all sort of dress up games for all ages. The copyright of these games are the sole property of their creators as we do not claim to have any rights upon the games hosted on our servers. Users agree that by submitting the game to us the physical file that is stored on our server is though our property and that we may decide to delete it, publish it or un-publish it without any previous announcement. 

If you think that someone is using your work and has stolen your creation please use the contact form in our contact page and write us a message containing the link to the page where you saw this copyright abuse and we will take immediate action to delete the game and report it to the proper authorities.

All the games published on Onlygirlsgames.com must follow the above rule and we can't be held responsible if those requirements are not met. 

**By playing on Onlygirlsgames.com and using this website, you consent with this Privacy Policy and you agree to be banned without any warnings if you are reported of missuse of our rules and terms. If you do not agree with our policy we politely ask you to stop using our system. You also agree that we may at any time change the contents of this Privacy Policy without any announcement.**

Thanks for visiting our Girls Games website. We provide, safe, fun games for girls and free games for everyone in many different game categories such as cooking games, dressup games, celebrity games and cartoon games.
